<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

    <ImageView
        android:layout_width="132dp"
        android:layout_height="115dp"
        android:background="@drawable/corovir"
        android:layout_marginTop="35dp"
        android:layout_marginLeft="240dp"/>

    <Button
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="110dp"
        android:backgroundTint="#00a2d8"
        android:text="Welcome"
        android:textColor="#fff"
        android:textSize="40sp"
        android:layout_marginTop="-150dp"/>

    <TextView
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="What would you like to do?"
        android:textAlignment="center"
        android:textColor="#007800"
        android:textSize="25dp"
        android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        android:layout_marginTop="60dp"/>

    <Button
        android:id="@+id/Search"
        android:layout_width="300dp"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
        android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
        android:background="@drawable/button_shape"
        android:text="Search for medical aid"
        android:textAlignment="center"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="20dp"
        android:textStyle="bold"/>

    <Button
        android:id="@+id/Self"
        android:layout_width="200dp"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
        android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="20dp"
        android:background="@drawable/button_shape"
        android:text="Self Diagnosis"
        android:textAlignment="center"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:textSize="20dp"
        android:textStyle="bold" />

    <Button
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:backgroundTint="#007800"
        android:text="Instructions for the patient"
        android:textColor="#fff"
        android:textSize="20dp"
        android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="30dp"/>

    <TextView
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:textSize="15dp"
        android:textColor="@color/black"
        android:paddingLeft="10dp"
        android:paddingRight="10dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        android:text="i. Patient must isolate himself from other household members, stay in the identified room and away from other people in home, especially elder lies and those with co-morbid conditions like hypertension, cardiovascular disease, renal disease etc.
        \n\nii. The patient should be kept in a well-ventilated room with cross ventilation and windows should be kept open to allow fresh air to come in.
        \n\niii. Patient should at all times use triple layer medical mask. Discard mask after 8 hours of use or earlier if they become wet or visibly soiled. In the event of care giver entering the room, both care giver and patient may consider using N 95 mask.
        \n\niv. Mask should be discarded only after disinfecting it with 1% Sodium Hypochlorite.
        \n\nv. Patient must take rest and drink lot of fluids to maintain adequate hydration.
        \n\nvi. Follow respiratory etiquettes at all times.
        \n\nvii. Frequent hand washing with soap and water for at least 40 seconds or clean with alcohol-based sanitizer.
        \n\nviii. Don’t share personal items with other people in the household.
        \n\nix. Ensure cleaning of surfaces in the room that are touched often (tabletops, doorknobs, handles, etc.) with 1% hypochlorite solution.
        \n\nx. Self-monitoring of blood oxygen saturation with a pulse oximeter is strongly advised.
        \n\nxi. The patient will self-monitor his/her health with daily temperature monitoring and report promptly if any deterioration of symptom as given below is noticed.
    "/>

            <Button
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:backgroundTint="#007800"
                android:text="Instructions for the Caregivers"
                android:textColor="#fff"
                android:textSize="20dp"
                android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
                android:layout_marginTop="30dp"/>

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textSize="15dp"
                android:textColor="@color/black"
                android:paddingLeft="10dp"
                android:paddingRight="10dp"
                android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:text="i. Mask:\n\to The caregiver should wear a triple layer medical mask. N95 mask may be considered when in the same room with the ill person.
\n\to Front portion of the mask should not be touched or handled during use.
\n\to If the mask gets wet or dirty with secretions, it must be changed immediately.
\n\to Discard the mask after use and perform hand hygiene after disposal of the mask.
\n\to He/she should avoid touching own face, nose or mouth.
\n\nii. Hand hygiene
\n\to Hand hygiene must be ensured following contact with ill person or his immediate environment.
\n\to Hand hygiene should also be practiced before and after preparing food, before eating, after using the toilet, and whenever hands look dirty.
\n\to Use soap and water for hand washing at least for 40 seconds. Alcohol-based hand rub can be used, if hands are not visibly soiled.
\n\to After using soap and water, use of disposable paper towels to dry hands is desirable. If not available, use dedicated clean cloth towels and replace them when they become wet.
\n\to Perform hand hygiene before and after removing gloves.
\n\niii. Exposure to patient/patient’s environment
\n\to Avoid direct contact with body fluids of the patient, particularly oral or respiratory secretions. Use disposable gloves while handling the patient.
\n\to Avoid exposure to potentially contaminated items in his immediate environment (e.g. avoid sharing cigarettes, eating utensils, dishes, drinks, used towels or bed linen).
\n\to Food must be provided to the patient in his room. Utensils and dishes used by the patient should be cleaned with soap/detergent and water wearing gloves. The utensils and dishes may be re-used.
\n\to Clean hands after taking off gloves or handling used items. Use triple layer medical mask and disposable gloves while cleaning or handling surfaces, clothing or linen used by the patient.
\n\to Perform hand hygiene before and after removing gloves."/>

        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>